

# Wojciech Świątek

Frontend Developer

## **PROFILE**

I'm Frontend Developer with more than 2 years of commercial experience in developing Web applications and Web sites in Vue and Laravel.

I've been interested in programming since my master's studies, starting from learning HTML, CSS and JS and later React.

I'm eager to learn. On free time I try to regularly take courses on platforms such as Udemy and listen to podcasts related to the IT industry.

### **EXPERTISE**

PHP Vue 2 Vue 3 API Vuex Git HTML<sub>5</sub> **Tailwind** 

**CSS3** Vuetify SASS Bootstrap

JavaScript (ES6+) SQL Laravel Docker

Figma Design Thinking Jira Design Sprint

Asana Agile CI/CD

# **LANGUAGES**

Polish - native English - B2 French - A1

React



**More information** 



# **PHONE** +48 793 074 448

**EMAIL** wojciechswiatek.lbn@gmail.com

**ADDRESS** 6 Inowrocławska 50/15. 53-648 Wrocław

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2023 - present Yax Interactive (Software House). Wrocław Developing customizable frontstore for online shopping (Vue).

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2022 - present Rating Captain, Wrocław

Developing SaaS application and landing page (Vue, Laravel).

#### JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Yax Interactive (Software House). Wrocław

Developing Web application and sites with responsive design, working with UX/UI designers.

#### **ASSOCIATE**

2018 - 2019 Koło Naukowe Pojazdów i Robotów Mobilnych Activity in the science club at Wroclaw University of Science and Technology.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Wroclaw University of Science And technology Faculty of Information Technology and Management Master of Science 2020-2021

#### **AUTOMATION CONTROL AND ROBOTICS**

Wroclaw University of Science And technology Faculty of Electrical Engineering Bachelor of Science 2016 - 2020

# **INTERESTS**









**Programming** 

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in the application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process in accordance with Art. 6 paragraph 1 letter a of the Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council (EU) 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).